So the first one,
来看第一个
the typo in David.
David 出现错误拼写
D_s_v_i_d versus D_a_v_i_d, and it's displayed here.
这里显示 D s v i d 而不是 D a v i d
This is an accuracy issue.
这是一个准确性问题
There's nothing illegal about having the name D_s_v_i_d,
并不是说 Dsvid 不可以作为一个人名
so it's not invalid, it's just inaccurate.
它本身并不是无效的 只是用在这里不正确
And the next one.
下一个
The letter U in the dosage information for Auralin and Novodra.
在 Auralin 和 Novodra 剂量信息中的字母 u
Once again, this is just the fact that the U is present.
同样 u 在这里客观存在
This is a validity issue.
这是一个有效性问题
23u is not a valid dose.
23u 不是一个有效的剂量
The valid dose is 23,
有效剂量是 23
and the unit of measurement is U,
它的测量单位是 u
or units, insulin units.
代表 unit (单位) 或者说 insulin unit (胰岛素单位)
We can't perform calculations with 23u.
我们不能用 23u 进行运算
This goes hand-in-hand with the wrong data type validity issue.
这与错误数据类型有效性问题紧密相关
But we'll physically have to remove the U,
但是我们必须删除 u
instead of just changing the data type.
而不是仅更改数据类型
Pandas won't accept something with the letter U in it as an integer or float.
Pandas 不会接受字母 u 作为一个整数或浮点数
It will force it to the data type object,
它将强制将其作为对象数据类型
which is how strings are represented in Pandas.
并表达为字符串
So again, this is invalid.
所以说 23u 是无效的
23u is right, it's just the wrong representation.
23u 本身是正确的 只是表示有误
It's not according to the defined schema of this table.
不符合该表所确定的模式
The next one, the lowercase given names and
下一个 治疗和不良反应表中
surnames and treatments and adverse reactions.
首字母小写的名字和姓氏
Treatments, adverse reactions.
这里是治疗表 这里是不良反应表
Let's zoom out a bit here.
我们在这里缩放一下
So I'd argue that this is a consistency issue.
这是一个一致性问题
It's not necessarily a big deal that the given names and surnames are in lowercase.
名字和姓氏首字母的大小写本身不是什么大问题
So that removes the inaccurate part.
不属于准确性问题
It's just that in the patients table,
但在患者表中
the names are capitalized.
姓名首字母用的大写
So you'd run into issues when joining these tables based on name.
如果根据姓名来联接这几个表 就会遇到问题
This is an inconsistent representation of name across tables in this dataset.
这是该数据集中的多张表的名称表述不一致问题
Pandas in Python doesn't recognize
Python 中的 Pandas
lowercase strings as the exact same as capitalized strings.
无法将小写字符串与大写字符串等同
So that's where the issue stems from.
这就是问题所在
And the final one: missing records in the treatments table,
最后一个是治疗表中缺少记录
280 instead of 350.
显示为 280 而不是 350
This is pretty straightforward,
显而易见
this is a completeness issue.
这是一个完整性问题
We don't have all the records that we need.
表中没有我们需要的所有记录